We finished step one,
完成了第一步
and we'll now start with step number two,
现在我们来进行第二步
which is finding the output y by using the values of h we just calculated.
用刚才求得的 h 值来求输出 y
Since we have more than one output,
由于我们的输出不止一个
y will be a vector as well.
所以 y 也是一个向量
We have our initial inputs h,
我们有初始输入 h
and want to find the values of the output y.
目的是借此求得输出 y 的值
Mathematically, the idea is identical to what we just saw in step number one.
从数学的角度看 第二步的过程和第一步一样
We now have different inputs,
现在我们的输入是 h
we call them h, and a different weight matrix, we call it W_2.
权重矩阵是 W2
The output will be vector y.
输出则为向量 y
Notice that the weight matrix has
注意 权重矩阵有三行
three rows as we have three neurons in the hidden layer,
因为隐藏层有三个神经元
and two columns as we have only two outputs.
两列 因为我们只有两个输出
And again, we have a vector by matrix multiplication.
还是一样 让向量和矩阵相乘
Vector h multiplied by the weight matrix W_2,
向量 h 与权重矩阵 W2 相乘
gives us the output vector y.
就能求得输出向量 y
We can put it in a simple equation where y equals h times W. Once we have the outputs,
我们可以把这个过程写成一个简单的方程式 即 y = h * W 得到输出后
we don't necessarily need an activation function.
不一定要用激活函数
To have a good approximation of the output y,
要很好地逼近输出 y
we need more than one level of hidden layers,
一个隐藏层是不够的
maybe even 10 or more.
我们需要十层 甚至更多
In this picture, I use the general number p. The number
这里我用 p 泛指 p 层
of neurons in each layer can change from one layer to the next,
每一层都可以有不同数量的神经元
and as I mentioned before,
正如我之前提到的
can be even thousands.
每一层都可以有数千个神经元
Essentially, you can look at these neurons as building
基本上 你可以把这些神经元
blocks or lego pieces that can be stacked.
看成可以堆砌的砖块或乐高积木
So how is this done mathematically? Just as before.
那这个过程要怎么转换成数学运算呢？ 就跟之前一样
A simple vector by matrix multiplication,
只需将向量和矩阵相乘
followed by an activation function,
然后将结果代入激活函数
where the vector indicates the inputs,
其中 向量为输入
and the matrix indicates the weights connecting one layer to the next.
矩阵为连接相邻两层的权重
To generalize this model,
我们来进行模型归纳
let's look into one random Kth layer.
来看一个随机 K 层模型
The weight W_ ij from the K layer to the K plus
其中连接 K 和 K + 1 层的权重 Wij
one corresponds to the ith input going into the jth output.
位于第 i 个输入与第 j 个输出之间
You might want to get a pencil for
你最好拿支笔做下笔记
this one as these are important mathematical derivations.
因为这是很重要的数学推导过程
As you follow the math,
你可以一边听数学推导
pause the video, write the derivations in your notes.
一边暂停 在笔记里将推导记录下来
Let's treat layer K as the inputs x,
我们把 K 层作为输入 x
and layer K plus one as the outputs of the hidden layer h. We will have n,
把 K+ 1 层作为隐藏层 h 的输出
x inputs and m, h outputs.
因此 我们会有 n 个 x 输入和 m 个 h 输出
By the way, if we are not dealing with inputs,
顺便提一句 如果我们处理的不是输入
but rather than the outputs of the previous hidden layer,
而是上一个隐藏层的输出
the only thing that will change is the letter that we choose to use,
那唯一要改的只有这些字母
but the calculations will be the same.
计算过程是一样的
So to make the notation simple,
所以我们用简单的表示符号就好
let's just stay with x. H one is the output of an activation function of a sum,
就还是 x 吧 h1 是一个激活函数的输出
where the sum is a multiplication of each input
该函数以
x_i by its corresponding weight component W_i1.
每个输入 xi 与相应权重 Wi1 乘积的和为参数
The same way h_m is the output of an activation function of a sum,
以此类推 hm 也是一个激活函数的输出
and the sum is the multiplication of each input
该函数以
x_i by its corresponding weight component W_im.
每个输入 xi 与相应权重 Wim 乘积的和为参数
For example, if we have three inputs,
举个例子 如果我们有三个输入
and we want to calculate h_1,
想要计算 h1 的话
it will be the output of an activation function of the following linear combination.
只需将下列线性组合代入激活函数 求得输出结果即可